那么如果我们把Fragment当做迷你Activity，每一个都
So if we treat fragments as mini activities, each with
有其独立的生命周期，它和
its own independent life cycle in UI, how does that compare
真正的Activity的生命周期有什么区别呢？
to the life cycle of a real activity? Well as
正如你所期望的 基本的生命周期事件和他的上层Activity
you might expect the basic life cycle events are much the
是一样的。并且当它在切换
same as the parent activity, and as it moves through
它的生命周期，开始、恢复、暂停、停止，状态时，相同的
the cycles of starts, resumes, pauses, and stops those same life
生命周期事件也会在Fragment当中触发。所以
cycle events will be triggered within the fragment itself. So,
在大多数情况下，你可以简单地把
in most cases, you can simply move anything that you would
本来放在Activity生命周期响应里的代码
have put into the activities life cycle handles,
移动到相对应的Fragment里面。当然，
into the corresponding fragment handles. With, of course, a
也有一些例外。与其在这onCreate里创建用户界面
couple of exceptions. Rather than building your UI here
Fragment为这个引入了一个新的特殊事件
and onCreate, fragments introduced a new event specifically for
onCreateView是用于创建或解析
this. OnCreateView is where you construct or inflate
你的用户界面，与数据进行挂钩
your UI, hook up to any data sources, and
并且将其返回给上层的Activity。然后它就可以
return it to the parent activity, which can then
集成到它的View的层次里。相对应的
integrate it into its view hierarchy. There's a corresponding
还有一个onDestroyView处理函数。它会在Fragment
onDestroyView handler, which is called immediately before the
被加入进后台堆栈之前被立即调用，独立于
fragment is added to the back stack, independent of the
它的上层Activity。现在记住Fragment
parent activity. Now keep in mind that the fragment
管理器可以添加任意的Fragment事务，添加、移除、或替换
manager can add any fragment transactions adding, removing, or replacing
到后台栈里面，只要简简单单一个上层
fragments to the back stack, with a single parent
Activity的动作。所以一个Fragment能够独立于
activity's actives. So a fragment can move through this
所属的Activity进行多次生命周期循环。
cycle multiple times independent of the host activity. So
所以在onDestroyView中，你应该清除所有的资源调用
onDestroyView is, where you should clean up any resources,
特别是与用户界面相关的，例如内存中的图片，
specifically related to the UI, such as bitmaps in
数据的游标，所有这类东西，来确保
memory, cursors to data, anything like that to help ensure
你的APP不会被不可见的Fragment
that your app's memory footprint isn't bloated by data that's
的数据占掉太多内存。现在只要
not needed when the fragment isn't visible. Now as soon
Fragment被从后台堆栈返回，onCreateView
as the fragment is returned from the back stack, onCreate
就会被调用到，然后你就可以赶在
view is called, and you can re-create the UI and
在你的Fragment将要变成Activity，也还没经过其他生命周期之前，
reconnect data sources before your fragment transitions through the rest
重新创建用户界面，并连接数据源。因为
of the life cycle to become active again. And because
一个Fragment只能存在于一个Activity里
a fragment can only exist within an activity,
我们还需要一个回调函数来告诉我们
we also need callbacks to tell us when a
一个Fragment何时被从它的上层Activity连接和分离。onAttach
fragment is attached and detached from its parent. onAttach
是获得它上层Activity引用的好机会。
is your opportunity to get a reference to the
而onDetach是最后发生的一个事件，
parent activity. While, onDetach is the last thing that
甚至在Fragment被销毁之后。
happens, even after your fragment has technically been destroyed.
现在这个难题的最后一块就是onActivityCreated
Now, the final piece of the puzzle is onActivity
它通知我们的Fragment上层Activity
created. This notifies our fragment that the parent activity
已经完成了它自己的创建处理函数并且标志着
has completed its own create handler and represents the point
我们可以安全地与其UI进行交互的时间点。潜在的，
at which we can safely interact with its UI. Potentially
也包括了其他Fragment。现在，就和我们在第三课讨论
including other fragments. Now, just like the activity lifecyle we
的Activity生命周期一样，一旦Fragment不再
discussed in lesson three, once the fragment is no longer
可见，它就有可能被终止
visible, there's a chance it will be terminated with no
而无需任何其他代码被执行。这可能在onStop之后发生，
further code being executed. That can happen, after onStop, in
当这个所属的Activity被终止了，而Fragment在他的
the case of the activity being terminated while the fragment
视图层级中的时候，或者在onDestroyView之后
is part of that activity's view hierarchy, or after onDestroy
当其所属Activity被销毁，而此时Fragment已经被放进了
view, if the fragment has already been placed
后台堆栈，也会如此。
in the back stack, once the activity is destroyed.